Barney 快看 八点方向\n有3个金发靓妞在喝闷酒
Check it:
Three blonde babies drinking\nbad decision juice at 8:00.
雷达真灵敏 这是我老婆（得瑟吧）
Nice rack radar.
- That's my wife.\n- No, I got to get going.
不 我得走了
真的? 她们可是喝醉的金发靓妞哦\n这不是你喜欢的型吗?
Seriously?\nBut they're blonde and drunk.
Isn't that your type?
或许我没有固定的型呢 Lily
Maybe I don't have a type, Lily.
天哪 你认为男人的脑子真有那么单纯
God, do you think\nthe male mind is really
that simplistic,
只喜欢一种类型? 天哪
that we all have one favorite type?
Geez.
大胸的亚洲妞\n（Barney喜欢的型）
Asian with some boob.
我去上个洗手间 然后闪了
I'm gonna hit the bathroom,\nthen bail.
好吧 你们有没发现Barney最近有点奇怪?
Okay, have you guys noticed\nBarney's been acting weird lately?
当然发现了
Actually, yes.
Barney老是声称决不会为姑娘买花
You know how he always says\nnever buy a girl flowers,
因为花有生命 会让她有想生娃的冲动\n你知道不?
'cause giving her a living thing\nreminds her babies?
当然
- Sure.\n- Well, the other day,
前几天 我看见他在82街的花店里买玫瑰
I saw him at that flower shop\non 82nd buying roses.
啥?
- What?\n- Now that you mention it,
等等 经你这么一讲\n昨天Barney在办公室确实举止怪异
Barney did do something kind of odd\nat the office yesterday.
好的 周六见
Okay, see you Saturday.
早午餐后去农贸市场溜一圈
I'm thinking brunch,\nfarmer's market, maybe a hike.
我也爱你 拜拜
I love you, too.
Bye.
我以为他正在钓妞
I figured he was just talking\nto some girl he was trying to nail.
或者在和Ted聊 现在我吃不准了
Or Ted, but now I don't know.
等等 Barney Stinson有女朋友了\n你们觉得可能不?
Wait, do you think it's possible\nthat Barney Stinson
has a girlfriend?
回见
Later.
等等 Barney 等下 你去哪?
Wait, Barney, hold on.\nWhere are you going?
没上哪儿 就海滩 冬天晒晒太阳\n还有玩镭射枪 回家
Nowhere.
The beach.\nIt's winter. Lazer Tag.
闭嘴 你才上别处混呢
Home. Shut up.\nYou're going somewhere.
我的天 他马上要和她幽会了
Oh, my God.
He's meeting her right now.
Barney去哪?
- Where is Barney going?\n- Yeah.
嗯 我们都出曼哈顿了
We're not even in Manhattan anymore.
那妞住哪?
Where's this girl live?
我们说的是\n让Barney Stinson就范的女人
We're talking about a woman\nwho's gotten Barney Stinson to commit.
我猜是Narnia\n（纳尼亚传奇）
I'm guessing Narnia.
哎呀 他停下来了
He's stopping.
- 你们来这搞什么?\n- 她在哪?
- What are you guys doing here?\n- Where is she?
- 谁?\n- 你的女朋友
- Who?\n- Your girlfriend.
你们好
哇哦 你的确是涉猎广泛啊?
You really don't have a type,\ndo you?
这些是我朋友 Ted Marshall Lily Robin
These are my friends.
伙计们 这是Loretta 我老妈
Guys,
this is Loretta.
- My mom.\n- It's so nice to meet you.
真高兴见到你们
感觉你们似曾相识啊
I feel like I already know you all.
Barney每天提到你们\n都会有如黄河之水连绵不绝
Barney goes on and on about you\nevery day when we talk.
你每天给你妈打电话?
You call your mom every day?
才不是 妈妈!
Mom!
你偷偷摸摸就为这?
So that's what you were being\nall secretive about?
你不想我们知道\n你老是个粘着妈妈的乖宝宝
You didn't want us to know\nyou're a big old mama's boy.
对 你们知道了 现在可以撤了吧
Yep, you got me.\nWell, guess you guys can leave.
你们好
Barney 这些是谁?
Who are all these people?
Ted Marshall Lily Robin
我向你们介绍Betty...
I'd like you to meet Betty...
我妻子
my wife.
还有我儿子Tyler
And my son Tyler.
Synchro: ShalimarFox, Arrow
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第15集
我和Betty准备好晚饭了
Betty and I are gonna get dinner ready.\nThere'll be plenty for everyone.
大家吃都绰绰有余了
但你 记着 只能吃一份肉饼哦
But remember you,
only one helping of meatloaf\nafter what Dr. Grossbard
Grossbard医生说你的胆固醇偏高
- said about your cholesterol.\n- This one wants me to live forever.
这人要我长生不老
罪过吧
Guilty.
- 我爱你\n- 我也爱你
- I love you.\n- I love you, too.
我也爱你们
- I love you three!\n- Get out of here, you little scamp!
快走 小捣蛋!
那我们回酒吧见?
- So, I'll see you guys back at the bar?\n- What the hell, Barney?
到底咋回事 Barney?
好吧 说来话长
OK, it's a long story.
我很小的时候 我爸就离开了我妈
As you know, my father\nhad to leave my mom
when I was a baby because he got hired\nas the host of The Price is Right.
因为他当上了"价格猜猜猜"节目的主持人
- 那节目确实不错\n- 嗯 Bob Barker是你爸
- It was a very good show.\n- Bob Barker is your father.
她一人把我和我哥拉扯大
She had to raise\nmy brother and me by herself.
她就盼望着儿子早日成家\n别像她一样
And her only wish was for her sons
not to wind up alone, like she was.
7年前 她病入膏肓
Then about seven years ago,\nshe got really sick.
貌似她快撑不过去了
It looked like\nshe wasn't going to make it.
所以 我决定实现她的愿望
So, I decided to make\nher wish come true.
妈妈 这是Betty \n我们订婚了
Mom.
This is Betty.\nWe're engaged.
我雇了个演员来演我的未婚妻Betty
I hired an actress
to play my fiance "Betty".
她的真名叫Margaret
Her real name's Margaret.
大多在外百老汇剧院演出 很棒的演员
She mostly does off-Broadway theater.\nWonderful actress.
差点就获得托尼奖(美国戏剧奖)\n你们知道那人的 很官方的奖
This close to a Tony.\nIt's all who you know.
我不该提到这 但问题是
It's very political.\nI shouldn't get into it.
But there's one problem.
Betty不怎么喜欢背台词
Betty has a slight tendency\nto go off-book.
看到了吧 妈妈? \n我找到了给我幸福的人
You see, Mom?\nI found someone who makes me happy.
正如你所希望的
Just like you wanted.
太好了
That's wonderful.
我只希望能活到抱孙子的那天
I just wish I could've stuck around\nlong enough for grandchildren.
我怀孕了!
I'm pregnant!
然后我妈妈康复了
And then my mom got better.
简直不可思议
Which was miraculous. But it meant\nthat I had to keep "Betty"
这就意味着我得留下"Betty"\n还得挑个娃演我儿子Tyler
around and cast a kid\nto play my son Tyler.
真荒唐 你真去挑选儿子了?
This is crazy.\nYou actually cast your own son?
开始我借用邻居的小孩
For a while,
I got by borrowing/babysitting\nmy neighbor's baby.
有年圣诞节 我妈在调蛋酒时
And this one Christmas,\nwhen my mom was plowed on eggnog,
我靠一袋面粉和一个查克面具过关了\n（装成宝宝的样子）
I got away with a bag of flour\nand a Chuckie mask.
但最后 我还得搞个试镜
But eventually,\nI had to hold auditions.
4号 8号...
Four,
eight...
13号 你们留下 还有的可以走了
13, you can stay.\nThe rest of you may go.
你说过要是我和你上床 \n就让我儿子演
You said that if I slept with you,\nmy son would get the part.
显然 我比你儿子演得好
Apparently,\nI'm a better actor than your kid.
11点复试!
Bring in the 11:00's!
然后Tyler的角色最后由...Grant演
And that's how the role of Tyler\neventually went to...
Grant.
还好啦 Grant貌似还不错
- Come on, Grant seems pretty good.\n- You think so?
你这么觉得? 看着
Watch this.\nHey, Tyler.
嘿 Tyler
Tyler
- Grant
- 嗯?
- Grant.\n- Yeah?
看见了吧? 完全不在行
See?\nIt's like amateur hour over here.
我荒唐吧 但比80年代的小孩演得好多了
Call me crazy, but child actors\nwere way better back in the'80s.
哇哦 Barney 看来你妈\n保留着你小时候的卧室
It looks like your mom kept
your childhood bedroom\njust the way you left it.
嗯 床上还贴着龙威小子的大海报
That sure is a big poster\nof The Karate Kid above your bed.
嘿 龙威小子是部很棒的影片
Karate Kid's a great movie.
关于一个满怀希望的小空手道迷梦想着
It's the story of a hopeful young karate\nenthusiast whose dreams and moxie
打遍空手道锦标赛无敌手的故事
take him all the way\nto the All Valley Karate Championship.
当然 悲哀的是\n在最后一轮输给了一傻帽
Of course, sadly, he loses\nin the final round to that nerd kid.
但他学会了心平气和地接受失败
But he learns an important lesson\nabout gracefully accepting defeat.
等等
Wait.\nWhen you watch The Karate Kid,
看龙威小子时\n你喜欢欺凌弱小的黄毛?
you actually root\nfor that mean blond boy?
如果不是 难道我喜欢从新泽西来的\n不懂空手道的瘦竹竿（其实他才是主角）
No, I root for the scrawny loser\nfrom New Jersey
who barely even knows karate.
我看龙威小子时 \n我喜欢的是真正的空手道小子
When I watch The Karate Kid,\nI root for the karate kid:
柯布拉・凯道场的约翰尼・劳伦斯
Johnny Lawrence\nfrom the Cobra Kai dojo.
清醒清醒吧 Lily
Get your head out of your ass, Lily.
好吧 我刚记起我在哪见过你
Okay, I just figured out\nwhere I know you from.
我在迷失剧院看过你演出
I saw you perform\nat the Disorientation Theater
去年秋天布莱希特之死
in Bertolt Brecht's Die Heilige\nJohanna der Schlachth felast fall.
我受益匪浅!
You were a revelation!
- 真的?\n- 嗯
- Really?\n- Yeah.
谢谢 我不确定
Thanks.
I wasn't sure. I mean, the point\nof Brecht's work, of course, is to...
我是说 布莱希特(德国戏剧家)\n的理论核心 当然 是用来...
转移观众注意力 的确 抱歉
Alienate the audience.\nSure.
Sorry.\nBrecht-o-phile right here!
布莱希特演剧理论!
你对剧院了解甚多啊
You really know your theater.
早年钟情于女性剧场后 难以割舍
Lady Theater grabbed my heart early on\nand she never let go.
每年圣诞节 我都会组织小孩为家长演出
Every year at Christmas,
I'd put on a little play for the parents\nwith all the other kids.
哎呀 圣诞老人 你觉得在\n这种暴雪中我们能着陆吗?
Gee whiz, Santa, do you think\nwe can take off in this kind of snow?
停! 停! 停! Ricky!
Cut! Cut!
Cut! Ricky!
爷爷奶奶过半小时就来了\n你台词还说不清楚
Grandma and Grandpa\nare gonna be here in half an hour,
and you're still butchering\nmy words.
看来我还得写明方向和星象
Looks like I'm gonna have to write,\ndirect and star in this thing.
把你的精灵帽给我 去坐下
Give me your elf hat.\nGo sit.
我老是暗想着想当名演员
I always secretly wanted\nto be an actor.
我想这只是我的春秋大梦罢了
It's one of those life dreams\nthat just slipped away, I guess.
听着 要是你想\n在表演方面 我可以给你支支招
Listen, if you want,\nI could give you some tips on acting.
- 真的?\n- 我很乐意
- Really?\n- I'd love to.
好的
表演规则第一条 不胆怯...
Acting rule number one...
至少还有人对演戏感兴趣
At least someone's still excited\nabout acting.
真怀念
I miss that.
你不喜欢演Barney的儿子?
So, you don't like playing\nBarney's son?
恨死了 但我又能咋样?
I hate it.\nBut what can I do?
也没别的好干
- The phone just ain't ringing.\n- I know what you mean.
嗯 我懂你意思 我是新闻播报员
I'm a newscaster.
我得早上四点半播报早新闻
But I just had to take a job\nhosting a local morning show
that airs at 4:30 in the morning.
我只是觉得这样碌碌无为不是我想要的
I just thought I'd be so much\nfurther along by this point, you know?
我都快30岁了
I'm almost 30.
别这样 你看上去还很不错
Come on, you still look great.
你鼻子整的不错
I love your nose job.
我鼻子没整过
I never had a nose job.
好吧 我也是
Right.
Me neither.
难以置信我们以前没见过你
I can't believe\nwe haven't met you before.
谁知道Barney有这么好的妈妈?
Who knew Barney\nhad such a great mom?
谢谢 亲爱的
Thanks, dear.
事实是 我年轻时不是个好妈妈
Truth is, I wasn't always\nthe best mother when I was younger.
别这么说 我确信您一直这么棒
Don't say that.\nI'm sure you were great.
嗯 我过去是妓女
Yeah, I was a bit of a whore.
啥?
Excuse me?
妓女 亲爱的 淫荡的妓女
A whore, dear.\nA dirty whore.
我觉得没啥光彩的
I'm not proud of it.
但...我还是过得很愉快
But...
still, I had some fun.
没什么激情能等同于...
There is no thrill equal to...
正视你的眼睛 想着"我不知你名 你不晓我姓
looking into some guy's eyes\nand thinking,
"I don't know your name,\nyou don't know mine, but...
只为那一刻销魂"
"for the next eight minutes,
"我们要把加油站的厕所掀翻"
"we are gonna rock\nthis gas station bathroom
"right off its foundation."
然后分道扬镳
And then just drive off\nin opposite directions.
各自开车飞驰
Just keep driving.
Barney的妈妈?
Barney's mom?
- Loretta\n- Loretta?\nLoretta.
不管咋样 那些 那些都是过去式了
Anyway, that's,\nthat's all in the past now.
我竭尽所能 但有时\n我会想Barney何以这么完美
I did the best I could, but...
sometimes I wonder how Barney\nturned out to be so perfect.
你得跟你妈说实话 好不?
You have to tell your mom\nthe truth, okay?
听着 她对你那么悉心照顾 关爱有加\n她该知道真相
Listen, she is a sweet,
caring, slightly too graphic woman\nwho deserves better.
不 不行 真相会要了她的命
No way. The truth would kill her.
我觉得欺骗这么\n善良的母亲真不道德 是不?
I don't feel right
about lying to such\na kindhearted woman, okay?
她 她让我想起了自己的母亲
She reminds me of my own mother.
- 啥?\n- 善良?
- What?\n- Kindhearted?
记得我们结婚宣誓时\n我说我们会永不分开吗?
Remember in our wedding vows\nwhen I said we'd be together forever?
我们从过道往回走时 你妈凑过来说
On our way back up the aisle,\nyour mother leaned in and she said,
"不会永远的 亲爱的 \nMarshall以后会去天堂"
"Not forever, sweetie.\nMarshall's going to heaven."
她只是开玩笑
- She was making a joke.\n- She hates me, Marshall.
她恨我 Marshall
不过也无所谓了 因为...\n没什么
But that's okay because...
Never mind.
不对 呃 怎么了? 你想说什么?
What were you gonna say?
没啥 嘿 想去Barney小时候\n那间房再做一次吗?
Nothing. Do you want to go do it\nin Barney's childhood bedroom again?
在我的赛车床上?
- On the race car bed?\n- Handles great, buddy.
那支把手巨爽 兄弟
听着 Lily 今天的事教给我们的
Look, Lily, if today has taught us\nnothing else, it's that
就是在家庭中坦诚是很重要的
honesty is important\nwhen it comes to family.
所以了 无论你对我妈的感觉如何
Now, whatever you're feeling\ntowards my mother,
我们...我们在一起12年了啊 宝贝
we've been together\nfor 12 years, baby.
我想我都能承受得了
- I think that I can handle it.\n- Really?
- 真的?\n- 当然
好吧
我恨你妈
I hate your mom.
好吧 你猜怎么着? 我恨你!
Guess what?
I hate you!
两分钟后烤肉卷就好咯!
Two minute warning for meatloaf!
烤肉卷? Tyler不稀饭!
Meatloaf?
Tyler no likey!
Grant 我说过一百万次了!
We have been over this\na million times!
你不是在做广告!
- You are not getting a catchphrase!\n- But it's funny.
可很好玩呐
Grant 你再这样我不介意换角的
I am not afraid to recast.
现在 边边去背晚餐场景的台词
Now go memorize your lines\nfor the big dinner scene.
等等 你都写好了晚餐的剧本了?
Wait. So you wrote the dinner\nwe're about to have?
嗯嗯 没错 只是个短篇剧本而已
Just a short script.
不过是些让我妈开心的对白
Just things that will make\nmy mom happy to hear.
什么对白?
What kind of things?
我还真的以为Barney\n忘了咱们的周年纪念日呢
And I really thought
Barney had forgotten\nour anniversary.
那时我冲出后院 气的耳朵都冒烟呐
So I storm out to the backyard,\nand there's smoke coming out of my ears.
鼻翼会开屏 她激动时鼻翼会开屏的\n我喜欢
Nostrils flaring. Her nostrils flare\nwhen she gets mad. I love it.
又来了 开屏了!
Doing it right now.\nDoing it right now!
放尊重点哦 先生!
You better stop, mister!
好好好 小熊熊 你继续
Sorry, sorry, boo bear. Continue.
这就是你喜欢的拍拖方式
This is what you're actually\nlike in a relationship.
然后呢 我冲出后院 看到...
So I storm out\nto the backyard and...
到处都是烛光 还有弦乐四重奏
candles everywhere...
and a string quartet.
- 你能相信吗?\n- 不 一点都不信
- Can you believe that?\n- No, not even slightly.
那我的小Ty-Ty怎么了 最近有什么趣事吗?
What about my little Ty-Ty.\nWhat have you been up to?
刚刚好 就那天晚上嘛\n这小淘气做了个噩梦
Funny story:
just the other night,\nthis little rascal had a nightmare.
那时他过来跟我们讲 \n还记得那时说了什么吗? 小帅哥
When he came in\nto tell us what it was about,
do you remember\nwhat you said, champ?
第四页
Page four.
呃 博物馆里面的恐龙化石活过来在追杀我?
The dinosaur bones in the museum\ncame to life and started chasing me?
多亏你了 兄弟 俺今晚别想睡了
Thanks a lot, buddy.\nI didn't need to sleep tonight.
不对 Tyler说"我做了个噩梦 \n梦见你和妈咪不清楚我有多爱你们
Tyler said, "My nightmare was
"that you and Mommy didn't\nknow how much I loved you.
所以我要来告诉你们 \n我是这~~么的爱你们
"So I wanted to come in\nand tell you it was this much."
好甜蜜哦
That's so sweet.
咱们是个甜蜜欢乐的家庭呢
We're a sweet happy family.
好吧 我现在去冰箱下格拿些冰淇淋出来
'm gonna grab some ice cream\nfrom the freezer downstairs
接着大家一起去厨房吃圣代咯
and then we'll all hit\nthe sundae bar in the kitchen.
哇 这场景没出一点差错哦 精彩
Not a weak link in that scene.
Bravo.
算了吧 Barney \n你都不知道跟着你做这码事有多难
Back off, Barney.\nYou have no idea how hard it is
to do a job that's beneath you.
Grant 我喜欢你说的恐龙骨头故事
I really enjoyed your thing\nabout the dinosaur bones.
能别再说恐龙骨头了吗?
Can we please stop talking\nabout the dinosaur bones?
去吃你的圣代吧
Just go eat your sundae.
吃不了 我有乳糖过敏
I can't.\nI'm lactose-intolerant.
知道谁没有乳糖过敏的吗? Tyler
Guess who's not\nlactose-intolerant? Tyler.
Tyler要乖乖地去厨房一口一口吃完它
Tyler is gonna go in there
and enjoy every last bite.
雪糕时间咯 大伙儿
Ice cream time, gang.
好吃耶!
Yummers!
我的天!
My God!
Tyler不稀饭
Tyler no likey.
都说不是在做广告啦
You're not getting a catchphrase.
我不懂
I don't understand.
我完全懂
I do.
配合我做
Follow my lead.
我被我最好的朋友背叛了
I've...
been betrayed
by my best friend.
你怎么敢这么做? Ted
How could you do this, Ted?
看看可怜的Tyler \n拼命不让眼泪流出来
Think about poor Tyler
bravely trying to hold back tears.
没事儿的 儿子 哭出来吧
It's okay, son, you can cry.
哭呀!
Cry!
我不想爹地妈咪离婚!
I don't want my mommy\nand daddy to get divorced!
你要怎么解释?
What could you possibly have\nto say for yourself?
表演注意事项第一则:\n别害怕临场发挥
Acting rule number one:
"Don't be afraid to improvise."
是我背叛了你吗? 是你背叛了我吧
Was it me who betrayed you,
or you who betrayed me?
不好意思 啥?
I'm sorry. What?
表演注意事项第五则:\n给你的角色创造个精彩的背景故事
Acting rule number five:
"Invent a rich back story\nfor your character."
1998年 10月14日
November 14th, 1998.
那天半夜 驶向蒙特卡洛的火车上
The overnight train to Monte Carlo.
我在桌球包厢里赢了\n几个阿尔及利亚佬几千第纳尔\n(阿尔及利亚货币单位)
I was in the billiards car
hustling some Algerians\nout of few thousand dinar,
而你却在那时勾引了我未婚妻!\nwhen you seduced my fiance!
她是盲的 还以为你是我
Who is blind and thought\nyou were me.
说得好
你到底在说什么?
What in God's name\nare you talking about?
表演注意事项第八则:\n不要害怕动作戏
Acting rule number eight:
Don't be afraid to get physical.
你个混蛋完全懂我在说什么!
You know damn well\nwhat I'm talking about!
不 我不懂!
No, I don't!
你懂的!
Yes, you do! And by God,
上帝啊 我听到你说话了 无赖!
I'll hear you say it, scoundrel!
妈 能让我们谈谈吗?
Mom, can you give us a sec?
好吧
- 那儿有巧克力和奶油糖果\n- 知道了 好...
There's chocolate and butterscotch.
上面还撒了好多不同的蜜饯
There's various kinds\nof sprinkles and marshmallows.
你脑残啊?
Have you lost your mind?!
你太棒了!
You were amazing!
简直把那角色演活了
You completely just became\nthat character.
坦白说 我没怎么本色演出\n反而努力摆脱了Ted的风格呢
Honestly,\nI wasn't so much playing Ted
as I was just trying\nto get out of Ted's way.
你们两个搞什么飞机?
What is wrong with you people?
Ted 你要我怎么跟我妈解释?
How am I ever gonna\nexplain this to my mother?
或者 是时候说出真相了 Barney
Maybe it's time\nto tell her the truth.
我不清楚哦 Lily \n真相会让人说出刻薄的话
I don't know, Lily.\nSometimes, honesty leads people
to say mean things about a woman\nwho always took special care of me
那个妇女可是从小对我特别好的
因为我是家里发育不良的一个
because I was the\nrunt of the family.
不怕你们笑话 我才1米93而已!
For crying out loud,\nI'm only six-four!
我哭得不错吧?
How good was my crying?
你成功了 看见了吧?
You nailed it.\nSee?
就算你不喜欢 你也能让自己做好的
Even at a gig you hate,\nyou still managed to love what you do.
或者你在新工作岗位上也能这样
Maybe that's how it will be\nfor you at your new job.
你真的这么觉得?
- You think so?\n- I know so.
- 我确信\n- 谢谢你 Grant.
Thanks, Grant.
你很聪明呢 知道吗?
You're pretty smart, you know that?
对不起! 对不起! 演过头了
Sorry! Sorry!
Thought I was picking up\non something.
亲爱的 你没事吧?
Honey, are you okay?
妈 有些事我要跟你说
Look, Mom,\nthere's something I have to tell you.
早就该跟你说的了
Something I should have\ntold you a long time ago.
Tyler快要死了
Tyler is dying.
Betty说如果他死了 她要跟他一起去
And Betty said that when he goes,
she's gonna off herself.
所以呢 这件事很快就会摆平了
So that's probably\nall gonna go down pretty soon.
老天啊!
Oh, my God!
好吧 不不! 所有都不是真的!
None of that is true!
真相是 我...
The truth is, I...
真相是Betty跟Tyler都是演员
The truth is Betty and Tyler\nare actors
是我雇他们假扮我家人的
that I hired\nto pretend to be my family.
什么?
What?
我只是想让你觉得我跟你期望的一样
I just wanted you to think\nI had the life
you wanted for me.\nI wanted you to be proud of me.
我想让你为我而骄傲
确实很疯狂 对不起了 妈
I know it sounds crazy,\nand I am so sorry, Mom.
这么说Betty不是你妻子咯?
So Betty is not your wife?
不是
太好了! 我讨厌那女人
Thank God!
I do not like that woman.
- 真的\n- 没错
- Really?\n- Yes.
还有Tyler...
And Tyler...
我是他奶奶 我应该喜欢他的\n可我就是讨厌那倒霉孩子
I know I'm his grandma\nand I'm supposed to love him,
but I hate that kid.
- "Tyler不稀饭!" 啥玩意儿啊这是?\n- 谁说不是啊?
"Tyler no likey!"
- What the hell is that?\n- Right?
还有你那五个假朋友 \n我真想一枪射死我自己
Those fake friends of yours out there,\nI just wanted to shoot myself.
我知道! 太糟糕了是吧?
I know!\nAren't they horrible?
这么说 你真的不生气?
So really, really, you're not mad?
我只是不明白
I'm just confused. I don't know\nwhy you thought you had to do this.
不明白为什么你要这么做
Barney 我爱你 有家庭也好没家庭也好
Barney, I love you, perfect\nfamily or no perfect family.
无论如何我都是爱你的
I love you no matter what.
- 真的?\n- 真的
- Really?\n- Really.
真的是轻松下来了 因为...
I am so relieved
because the truth is\nI am as far from married
我是个在人类中离婚姻最远的人
as a human being can possibly be.
我的情爱史会吓坏你的
My history with women\nwould shock and appall you.
无所谓 我还是爱你的
Doesn't matter.\nI still love you.
说真的 你真的想象不了我的荒唐事
Seriously, you can't imagine\nthe things I have done.
Barney 你三岁时我把你留给保姆照顾
Barney, when you were three,\nI left you with a babysitter
像个锣一样被Grand Funk Railroad\n"敲打"了整整三个星期\n(七十年代重金属乐队)
and spent three weeks\nwith Grand Funk Railroad
being passed around like a bong.
妈咪?
Mommy!
帮我个忙
Just do me a favor.
如果遇见了哪个特殊的人 不要放过她\n不要像我那样
If you ever do meet someone special,
don't run away from it.\nDon't be me.
试着走出那一步 好吗?
Take a shot at it, will you?
嘿 Barney 计程车来了
Cab's here.
我会的
I'll try.
这就是我们渡过的最奇怪的一个下午
And so ended one of the strangest\nafternoons of our lives.
我只是想跟你说
And I just wanted to say to you,
如果我表现得很冷漠或者不愉快的话\n对不起
if I ever seemed cold
or unwelcoming, I'm sorry.
- 她在跟谁说话呢?\n- 我妈
Who's she talking to?
My mom.
如果咱们俩可以再亲近点就太好了
It would mean a lot to me\nif you and I could be closer.
深呼吸一口装作难以开口的样子
Now take a deep breath like this next\nthing is gonna be hard to say.
- 我爱你\n- 我爱你...
I love you.
I love you...
- 妈妈\n- 没错
Mom.
妈
... Mom.
现在装作我说了什么亲切的话
Now pretend I said something nice.
我是说 你这么说真好 Judy
I mean,
that's very nice\nof you to say, Judy.
好吧 你也是哦 再见
You, too.\nSpeak soon.
我直说吧
Let me get this straight.\nYou're really telling me
你看龙威小子时候\n不是站在Daniel-san这边的?
that when you watch The Karate Kid,
you don't root for Daniel-san?
不
虎胆龙威里你支持谁?
- Who do you root for in Die Hard?\n- Hans Gruber,
Hans Gruber 性感的国际大盗
charming international bandit.
电影最后 他死定了(die hard)
At the end, he died hard.
他才是主演呢
He's the title character.
好吧 早餐俱乐部呢?
Okay, The Breakfast Club?
罚人留堂的那个老师
The teacher running detention.
他可是全电影里唯一穿西装的
He's the only guy\nin the whole movie wearing a suit.
我想到了一个 终结者
I got one.\nTerminator.
这电影叫什么名字? Robin
What's the name of the movie, Robin?
最后他的小红眼就算\n掉出来了都没掉过一滴眼泪
Who among us didn't shed a tear
when his little red eye\nwent out at the end
而且追杀那些人还失败了
and he didn't get\nto kill those people?
对不起我失态了 那电影真是...
I'm sorry.\nThat movie...
我再也不跟你看电影了
I am never watching a movie\nwith you ever again.
他们甚至没想过要帮他!
They didn't even try to help him!